"Kissing at High Tide"
When I used to laugh
I can feel a sense of distance
There is a layer of fog in the smile
But
It's different now
Brother can really laugh happily
and warm
And sincere
that moment
my heart
Fall all of a sudden
Brother
do you know
your smile
More dazzling than anything else
that smile
can really make me
into your heart
when you read a book
What I like best is standing next to you and cooking for you
That kind of ordinary moment
But in my world
the most real happiness
Just like this heat
my heart
Also quietly surrounding you
I'm making a fuss
when you laugh again and again
Just you love me
It's also proof that I love you
what are you doing
you
Are you a little dissatisfied with me recently?
Then do it yourself, Chef-sama
I don't want to eat it myself
You should try it too
How is it
What does it taste like this time?
sweet
Everything I give you is sweet.
That's weird
What are you doing? It's so cold.
The moment I saw you put on Ruby's apron
I just understand
Even the coldest person
I will slowly melt for one person
And that person
it's me
what is this
Critical illness notification letter sent from the hospital
piece of paper
Why does it hurt so much
Dr. David
Now I want to book a ward
Right now
To VIP-1
I personally guarantee
why
You want to help me like this
because i want to
what i want is
when you want to cry
The first person that comes to mind is me
Brother
There is something I really want to say to you
Can I really rely on you?
me
Not that strong actually
Still a little unfamiliar
It always makes you angry
But
Brother
you are always by my side
I am used to being alone
Now I always want to rely on you
Brother
Is this really okay?
me
Can I really rely on you completely?
Haijun
look at me
It'll be fine
I will definitely protect you
all the things you care about
Mom will be fine
It will be safe for sure
This is not comfort, this is a promise
So don't cry alone anymore
don't be sad anymore
From now on, your business is my business
Protect your smile
That's why I live
So please put you and your future
Leave it to me
I'm willing to do anything for you
©2025 SEEKMedia All Rights Reserved